darkhorse.com 2009-09-02

# Privacy :: Dark Horse Comics

By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of Dark Horse Comics, Inc. If you do not agree to the Policy, please do not use this site. 

Dark Horse Comics, Inc. recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to its site on the Internet. Specifically, we recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about our visitors. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or email address, is automatically collected from visitors to our site. We may collect certain non-personal information used only to optimize our web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser and the type of operating system you use). We may also use non-personal information to determine the total number of visitors to our website. 

Personally-identifiable information about visitors to the Dark Horse Comics, Inc. site is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. In those instances when we do collect such information, the following applies: 

**Policies for Individuals Under the Age of 18**  
Dark Horse Comics, Inc. encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on this site. No information should be submitted to web sites by visitors under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

**Notice**  
We will notify you when we are collecting personally identifiable information about you, as well as the uses we intend to make of that information. For example, when you sign up for an account on this website we need to collect your information. 

**Use and Security**  
Personally identifiable information that is submitted knowingly and voluntarily by visitors to our site is retained by Dark Horse Comics, Inc., and is not sold or otherwise transferred. However, Dark Horse Comics, Inc. may share personally identifiable information with other parts of our company. Dark Horse Comics, Inc. maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of such information. In addition to using information about you to respond to your specific requests, we may use it in aggregate form to make our site better and more responsive to the needs of our visitors. This statistical compilation of non-identifiable information may also be used by Dark Horse Comics, Inc. or provided to others for marketing, advertising or research purposes. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
This site may be linked to other sites operated by companies affiliated with Dark Horse Comics, Inc. or by others. Dark Horse Comics, Inc. is not responsible for the content or practices of third party web sites that may be linked to this site. Visitors to the sites operated by affiliated companies should refer to the privacy policies posted on those sites. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Dark Horse Comics, Inc. reviews its privacy policy periodically, and it may be subject to change.
